Does your soul die a little every time you throw away unused food?
每当你扔掉没吃的食物时，你的灵魂是否会有点难过？
Mine does.
我的就会。
Maybe that feeling comes from growing up in South Africa, where the phrase “there are children starving in Africa” was more of an uncomfortable reminder of fact than a prayer at dinner time.
也许这种感觉来自我在南非长大的经历，在那里，“非洲有孩子在挨饿”这句话与其说是晚餐时的祷告，不如说是对现实的一种令人不安的提醒。
Food waste is a growing concern in the restaurant, supermarket, and supply chain industries.
食物浪费日益成为餐饮、超市和供应链行业关注的问题。
From technological solutions to educational campaigns, food producers and sellers are looking for ways to use more of what we’re already growing.
从技术解决方案到教育活动，食品生产商和销售商都在寻找办法，更充分地利用我们已经种出来的东西。
But last month, one popular New York City restaurant tried a different way: It changed its menu to exclusively offer food that would otherwise be thrown away.
但上个月，纽约市一家很受欢迎的餐厅尝试了一种不同的方式：它更换了菜单，专门供应那些原本会被扔掉的食物。
For three weeks in March, Greenwich Village’s Blue Hill restaurant was renamed wastED, and served items like fried skate cartilage, a juice pulp burger, and a dumpster diver’s vegetable salad.
三月份的三周里，格林尼治村的蓝山餐厅更名为“wastED”，供应油炸鳐鱼软骨、果汁残渣汉堡和“翻垃圾箱者”蔬菜沙拉等菜品。
Each dish was tailor-made to raise awareness regarding food waste.
每道菜都是为提高人们对食物浪费的认识而量身定做的。
A study by the Food Waste Reduction Alliance determined that the average restaurant generates 33 pounds of food waste for every $1,000 in revenue, and of that waste only 15.7% is donated or recycled.
“减少食物浪费联盟”的一项研究发现，平均每家餐厅每创造1000美元收入，就会产生33磅食物垃圾，其中只有15.7%被捐赠或回收。
The remaining 84.3% is simply thrown out.
其余的84.3%被直接扔掉。
Restaurants like Silo in the UK have experimented with zero-waste systems, but wastED took the concept to its logical conclusion.
像英国的 Silo 这样的餐厅尝试过零浪费系统，但 wastED 把这一理念贯彻到底。
It should be noted that none of the items on wastED’s menu was technically made from garbage.
需要指出的是，wastED 菜单上的菜品严格来说没有一样是用垃圾做的。
Instead, all the ingredients used were examples of meat cuts and produce that most restaurants would never consider serving.
相反，所用的食材都是大多数餐厅从来不会考虑供应的肉类部位和农产品。
Things like kale ribs, fish collars, rejected sweet potatoes, and cucumber butts were all re-appropriated and, with the help of a number of good chefs, turned into excellent cuisine.
像羽衣甘蓝茎、鱼颈肉、被淘汰的红薯和黄瓜蒂这样的东西都被重新利用，并在一批优秀厨师的帮助下，变成了精美的菜肴。
Though wastED received enthusiastic reviews, it was designed from the start as a short-lived experiment; Blue Hill has since returned to its regular menu.
尽管 wastED 获得了热烈的好评，但它从一开始就被设计成一次短期实验；此后蓝山餐厅已经恢复了常规菜单。
Nevertheless, it serves as a reminder that there are many ways to address problems of sustainability, and that you can make an amazing meal out of almost anything.
尽管如此，它提醒我们：解决可持续性问题的方法有很多，而且几乎用任何东西都能做出一顿美味佳肴。